Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Hurry up, Moo! Are you coming yet?
We’re running late!
Hurry up!
Moo!
Get on quickly.
Hey, make sure I arrive in time.
Yes, you’ll get there in time.
Hold on tight.
Okay.
Watch out!
Keep going.
Alright.
[New Wave Project Audition, Central Region Qualifying Round]
Moo.
Go get ‘em.
I will.
Can you take this?
I have to go.
Hurry.
Kang.
Give me a hug. I need some encouragement.
I’m going now.
Go kill it.
I’m rooting for you.
You have 10 seconds.
EP 1: CHANGE
SEVERAL MONTHS EARLIER
Is he still not here yet?
I’m giving him 10 more minutes.
I’m not going to wait any longer than that.
I’m running late.
I’ve finished.
Hey, you can’t leave yet!
Close the room.
Hi.
Are you ready?
I am.
(This is me, Moo.)
(An ordinary guy who dreams of becoming an idol.)
(Clearly, the journey to my dream is no bed of roses.)
(It's a bed of thorns.)
(For as long as I can remember, I’ve loved dancing.)
(I got my inspiration from being on stage and seeing the audience clap for me.)
(I discovered my dream in life.)
(My dream is to dance.)
(You think I’m the center of attention?)
(I’m just an extra dancer.)
(Something always gets in the way of reaching my dream.)
(But wait and see, this time I’ll make it happen.)
I’m hearing back so quickly. I definitely passed.
What the hell?
[You did not pass the contest.]
I even randomly guessed the answers and left the exam.
Moo.
[You did not pass the contest.]
Yes, Mom.
Why did you only get back now?
I went to tutoring classes after the exam.
Many subjects.
Are you sure you went to tutoring classes?
Yes.
Give it to me.
Give me your backpack.
Mom.
Give it.
What subject is this?
Physics.
Chemistry.
Biology.
Biology?
You better learn not to lose your life.
You skipped school to audition again, didn’t you?
No, Mom.
Thank you.
You did really great.
I think you have a bright future ahead of you.
Our team will get back to you.
I didn’t want to lie to you
but if I pass this audition, I’ll get to become an idol for sure.
You’re so afraid of failing the audition that you’re willing to fail the exam?
How did you know that?
Let’s talk about how you did your exam
because you’re not interested in being smart.
The teacher called me.
Prepare to retake the exam.
If you don’t pass this subject, you won’t graduate.
Moo, if you keep ignoring your studies like this,
you’ll regret it one day.
Studies can be your plan B.
But I don’t want a plan B.
My only goal is to become an idol.
It’s my fault for being too easy on you that you got used to it.
I let this go on for too long that you became so stubborn.
Your grades have been dropping since you started grade 10.
You’re now in the first semester of grade 12 and they’re not getting better.
I guess I have to give you a harsh punishment this time.
Mom, are you really going to punish me this way?
Yes.
You will move to a school out of town.
You will live far away you can’t skip school and go dancing anywhere.
Grab that.
And this semester…
Careful.
And if you ignore your studies this semester and fail to get into university,
you can forget about dancing.
Mom, tell me honestly.
Why don’t you want me to dance?
Because I love you.
I’m in the industry.
Outsiders think it’s beautiful
but it’s actually not pleasant to be in.
You’d have to sacrifice a lot more than you think.
Trust me.
You can’t be an idol forever.
When you turn 30, 40, and 50, your time is up.
Mom,
I don’t know what I want to be at those ages
but I know what I want to be now.
No more talking.
It’s just one semester.
Go and study there so there’s no entertainment to distract you.
Just focus on doing well in school and passing the university admission exam.
That’s enough.
End of story.
Mom.
You won’t change your mind no matter what I say, right?
If your dream is really important to you,
you must do what I ask.
Consider this one of the tests you have to pass to reach your dream.
Get in the car.
Thank you so much.
Ride safe.
I will.
See you around.
Oh, Kang!
Why did it take you more than two hours to come back from the market?
What took you so long?
We might not be able to finish preparing the food in time for sale.
I ran into Auntie Pu at the market.
I saw she had been waiting for a ride for a long time.
I’m rich and have a lot of gas, so.
Okay, philanthropist.
Go and wash the vegetables before I smack you.
Yes, Mom.
Can you manage?
Yes.
Smack me.
Is that ready?
I’ll be back.
Okay.
Here’s your food, Uncle Auan.
And please let your daughter eat this for nourishment.
I prepared it especially for her.
Thank you, Mr. Kang.
Hey, Kang.
Hey, Neth.
Hello, Miss Neth.
Hi, Uncle Auan.
I’m going to eat if you don’t mind.
Come here.
Come here!
What is it, Neth?
My dad doesn’t pay him a small salary.
You don’t have to give him food every day.
But he still makes less money than us.
It’s fine.
It’s no big deal.
My family happens to be rich.
Okay, rich kid.
You give him one meal a day which costs 40 baht.
The total per month is 1200 baht.
That’s not a small amount of money.
It’s only 40 baht to make the world a nicer place.
It’s worth it.
How noble you are.
Of course, I am.
What’s wrong with you?
Mom, is this really Nakhon Pathom?
I haven’t seen Phra Pathom Chedi.
We didn’t pass Jae Kaek’s either.
You said we’d arrive in no time
but you’d been speeding for 3 hours.
This is the right place.
You’ll be far away from all the city distractions and only focus on your studies.
Are you sure there’s a school around here?
Yes. It’s not far.
You can walk there.
Just head that way.
That way?
Yes.
Are you sure you’re not punishing me too harshly?
Harshly?
I chose what’s best for you.
I went to this school too back in the day.
I graduated and became quite successful.
I walked to school.
While walking, I recited vocabulary and the periodic table.
It was so good.
Don’t make that face.
Nowadays is so much better than back then.
When I booked the dorm, the owner said a convenience store was only a 20-minute walk.
Back in my days, it took me an hour to go shopping in the city.
You’ll be fine, right?
Yes. I’ll be totally fine.
No sweat.
Definitely no sweat.
I’m leaving then.
Okay. Bye.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Come visit me.
I’ll have to check my schedule.
I’m leaving now.
You’re leaving now?
I’m leaving.
Okay. Bye.
Love you.
When I run out of toothpaste, I have to travel 20 minutes?
These are so damn heavy.
Hi.
My mom called and booked a room.
Oh, you’re moving in, right?
Yes.
Just a moment.
The key.
5th floor. Room 501.
When you arrive on your floor, your room will be to your left.
No noise after 10 p.m.
That’s it.
Thank you.
Where’s the elevator?
There’s none.
Take the stairs.
5th floor?
Yes.
5th floor.
It’s only the 5th floor.
Oh.
Will you be alright, kid?
If not, keep going anyway.
This is easy. It’s only 5 floors.
It’s easy!
Only one floor to go. It’s easy!
What did I bring?
Shit.
This is the Zen way.
So minimal.
Hey, this is too minimal.
(What an absolute crap.)
(This is the only entertainment left in my life.)
(People in the past could live without the internet.)
(I’ll survive too.)
You can do it, Mok.
(Luckily, I was careful and didn’t forget my shower cream.)
But I didn’t bring my shampoo.
Come on. I can do a 20-minute workout.
Shit. There’s no tissue paper.
There’s no water.
3 trips are enough. I’m not going there again.
I have no toothbrush.
Why am I so forgetful?
[Mommy Kai’s Rice and Curry]
[Catering Service Available for Events and Ceremonies at Affordable Prices]
These are 50 each for 2 with a side of eggs.
It’ll be 100 baht as usual.
The water is free.
Here’s 100 baht exact.
Thanks.
Please come again.
My mom asked me to give you an offering envelope.
Thanks.
I’ve received many envelopes this month.
Please come again.
Mom, you can leave it there. I’ll do it.
No need.
Keep drawing.
I’ll clean up myself.
Here.
Can you put this in a drawer?
I’ll lie down a bit.
Excuse me.
Hmm?
Do you have a toothbrush for sale?
You want to buy a toothbrush at a rice and curry restaurant?
It’s okay if you don’t have it.
I have it.
Just a moment.
It’s surprisingly available.
Here.
Thank you.
How much is this?
2 million.
Huh? 2 million?
If you don’t have that much money, you don’t have to pay.
A toothbrush shouldn’t cost as much as 2 million.
Stop.
Don’t move.
It’s just a mosquito.
You startled me.
You could’ve told me there was a mosquito.
I would’ve slapped it.
Why would you slap it?
You can just shoo it away.
Can I help you with anything else?
Is there a bicycle shop around here?
(What? He looks like he doesn’t want to tell me.)
Damn! This is so far.
I thought he said it was around here.
What’s wrong with my internet?
Which way do I go next?
I don’t know.
It’s hot.
Oh, hey.
I thought you said it was around here.
I can’t find it.
I knew you would get lost.
Get on.
Are you giving me a ride?
I guess I rode here to say hi.
Hurry up. It’s hot.
Thank you.
Oh, this really is a bicycle shop.
I told you it was nearby.
Thank you.
You’re so kind.
No.
This will be 2 million.
Plus another 2 million for the toothbrush from earlier.
You’re kidding, right?
I didn’t expect you to believe it.
You should smile a lot.
You look so cute when you smile.
Why is my face your problem?
Just go in.
I’ll wait outside.
Okay.
I look kinda cute when I smile.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What do you think?
This is so cool, isn’t it?
If you want to look cool, let me know.
I’ll let you borrow it.
Do you even know how to ride it?
Yes.
Can your feet touch the ground?
Of course.
I’m not going to fall off.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
I’m sorry.
I should be the one to say sorry.
Why would you say sorry?
It was an accident.
But you apologized to me first.
That’s true.
I was a bit too careless.
I’m not used to this.
Off you go.
I can’t go.
You’re holding my hands.
I have to go take care of something.
Do you remember the way back?
Yes, I’ll be totally fine.
Be careful though.
My bike is powerful.
You might not be able to keep up.
It was an accident. It was an accident.
It was an accident.
Let’s go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Shrimp Paste Fried Rice?
Cute.
Me?
I meant the picture.
If only you’d started school this year, you’d do well.
Stop talking about this.
I made my decision a long time ago.
Kang,
come help me carry…
- Okay.
- Neth!
Have you eaten?
Not yet, Mom. I’m hungry.
Let me fix you up.
Don’t cook for her, Mom,
or she’ll eat up all the rice in the cooker.
This one is a greedy eater.
You’re so mean to your friend.
Can I have two fried eggs?
You got it.
By the way, where did you go?
I dropped someone off at the bicycle shop.
Who?
I don’t know.
He randomly walked in here and asked if I had a toothbrush for sale.
Then he also asked me if there’s a bicycle shop nearby.
Oh, the Asian-looking boy, right?
Yes.
He’s my new tenant.
He’s from Bangkok.
His mom just dropped him off this morning.
But it seems to me
his mom sent him here to discipline him.
He looks like a troublemaker.
Discipline?
When I met him, he didn’t seem like a bad person.
Oh, you innocent guy.
Even you, who seem like a good guy, have a bad mouth.
You’re no different.
Neth.
Neth, dear
Yes?
Your rice is ready.
It’s warm and nice.
Thank you, Mom.
Come.
See, Mom?
She’s going to suck us dry.
2 fried eggs, right?
Here you go.
Can you really finish it?
Yes, I can.
Thank you.
Your body is still in great shape.
[Mommy Kai’s Rice and Curry]
Thank you.
Why is he not back yet?
Hey.
What happened?
A frog ran in front of me.
I veered off and the chain came off.
I also got this wound.
You have to live with it.
The young frogs are impatient around here.
They always run in front of people’s vehicles.
Thank you.
If it weren’t for you, I’d be in a tough situation.
Don’t thank me.
I’m charging you for everything.
I’ll put it on your tab later.
Hey.
Where are you taking my bike?
You think you can ride in that state?
You won’t even be able to walk back.
Why are you still sitting there?
Get on.
Do you want to go back to your dorm or not?
Yes.
We’ve arrived.
Yeah.
How do I get this off?
Come on. Let me help.
Thank you for helping me and dropping me off all the way here.
Do you have something in your room to clean your wound?
See you later then.
Go put your bike away.
I’ll wait at my restaurant.
Okay.
You’re overreacting.
I’ll put it away myself.
He’s quite kind.
Ouch. That stings.
It will sting a bit.
It hurts.
Don’t move.
Done.
Thank you.
If it weren’t for you, I’d be in a bad condition.
I was just worried your wound would rot
and you’d have to cut off your arm.
The doctors are busy around here.
I don’t want to give them more work.
Hey.
Hmm?
Your restaurant is still open, right?
Of course.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
Wow.
This is my dream fried egg.
Why are you so skilled?
Calm down. It’s just a fried egg.
I’m serious.
Just by looking at it, I can tell it’s a crispy fried egg.
Look at this.
The egg yolk is undercooked.
This is the correct fried egg by international standards.
This is not a waste of being a fried egg.
It’s so yummy.
Did your mom leave you with a phone when you were a kid?
Your reaction is so over the top.
It’s just a fried egg but you rave so much about it.
You’re not originally from Nakhon Pathom, right?
No.
I just moved here from Bangkok.
I transferred here for 12th grade.
So you’re sent here to correct your behavior.
Oops.
You talk like you knew.
This is literally so delicious.
I’m not kidding.
How much is the food?
I’d usually charge 1,000 baht
but you said it’s delicious
so I’m only charging you 45 baht.
Alright.
Do you accept a bank transfer?
Sure.
But I don’t know if the internet signal is good.
The signal at your restaurant is better than in my room.
I don’t want to complain, but there’s only one bar upstairs.
I’ll find an excuse to come and use the internet here again.
Just a moment.
[Available Balance: 30.50]
What’s up, Moo?
The day is not over yet and you’re missing me already?
I miss you.
Mom, can you transfer money to me?
I spent all the money to buy a new bike.
How is that possible?
Your account has like 10,000
and I already transferred an additional 5,000 for this month.
My bike cost almost 20,000.
What kind of crazy bike cost 20,000?
I didn’t send you there to live comfortably day by day.
You have to be frugal.
Do you understand?
You’re not supposed to spend your time going out.
Mom, I’m not going out.
The bicycle is an essential item.
Without it, I’d have to walk until my legs hurt.
I don’t know and I won’t give you any more money.
I already transferred you this month's allowance.
I’ll transfer again next month.
You must survive.
This is your test.
Mom! But I really don’t have money.
Mom!
Are you really not going to give me money?
Please, Mom!
Mom!
Mew, my best friend, do you have one or two thousand baht I could borrow?
I’m really broke right now.
Hello, Pike.
Can I borrow 1,000 baht?
Hello, Wit.
Damn it!
If you’re going to pay me with this many coins, I don’t want it.
No one is having an ordination ceremony.
Keep them for the water vendor machine.
I only have coins and these are all I have.
You can pay me later.
Really?
Will you really let me pay later?
I promise I won’t run from my debt.
I’ll definitely pay you back one day.
Are you sure? You owe me 10 million already
for the toothbrush, the ride, fixing your bike, dressing your wound, and the food.
Are you serious?
I thought you were joking.
I’ll put it on your tab.
What’s your name?
Are you tricking me into telling you my name?
Your name is Little Brat.
My name is Moo.
What’s your name?
You have no right to ask.
Why do you want to know?
So I can make a note on my phone of who I owe money to
but if you don’t tell me your name,
I’ll write that I owe money to Bad-Mouth-Kind-Heart Bro.
I’m not kind.
You gave me the toothbrush,
took me to the bicycle shop,
fixed my bike, dressed my wound,
and gave me food.
If that’s not kind, should I call you Cute Bro instead?
You’re not Little Brat, but Pain in the Neck.
I call it quick-witted.
Argumentative.
Please stop.
Even though I owe you money and can’t pay you back,
let me repay you by doing what I do best.
♪ My heart sparks when you turn around ♪
♪ Once our eyes meet, I’m so down ♪
♪ I’m not one to fall easily ♪
♪ But my heart’s in trouble now, you see ♪
♪ I’m all yours only ♪
♪ Yours only ♪
Ouch!
It hurts.
Thank you.
(Mosquito. Of all the places to bite, you’re biting my face?)
(You’re going to get it.)
Stop!
Why would you slap it?
You can just shoo it away.
(You’re lucky the cute guy’s words saved your life, little mosquito.)
(Go away.)
[Little Brat Pain in the Neck, Argumentative]
My name is Moo.
What’s your name?
Why do you want to know?
So I can make a note on my phone who I owe money to
but if you don’t tell me your name,
I’ll write that I owe money to Bad-Mouth-Kind-Heart Bro.
I’m not kind.
You gave me the toothbrush,
took me to the bicycle shop,
fixed my bike, dressed my wound,
and gave me food.
If that’s not kind, should I call you Cute Bro instead?
[MOMMY KAI’S RICE AND CURRY]
What are you drawing, son?
Oh.
You’re drawing our restaurant?
I’m practicing coloring.
It’s quite hard.
If you mess up on coloring on this kind of paper, you can’t fix it.
You’re right.
Dad.
Hmm?
I want a tablet.
A tablet?
What would you use a tablet for?
You just draw casually.
Mom,
how many times have I told you I don’t draw casually?
Are you serious about getting into art school?
You might want to think it over.
What’s wrong with me wanting to study art and become an artist?
Kang.
Take it easy.
Your mom just wants you to take time to think about this.
You still have time.
Yes.
Kind?
I don’t think so.
♪ You tell me not to take it seriously, but you secretly do ♪
♪ A bit cuter than this and I’ll become your slave ♪
Hey.
Why is he wearing a jacket?
Won’t he die of heat?
What a poser.
Judging from his look, he must have gotten expelled.
Hey, kid.
Yes?
This is my usual parking spot.
Move.
I don’t see any names here.
First come, first served.
Why are you talking like this?
You must be new.
That’s why you don’t know who we are.
Who are you guys?
We’re the people you don’t want to cross
because we can make your life here a living hell.
You think you’re so important?
What?
What are you doing to my bike?
Hey.
Don’t fight!
Nothing is going on, Mr. Security Guard.
Hello, Director.
Hi.
Do I look like a security guard?
[Pathom Pittaya School]
Oh.
Okay.
Remove it.
You’re here to study, not to look handsome, okay?
If you want to look handsome, do that outside the school.
Your last semester grades from your previous school weren’t very good.
But I think I did much better than when I was in grade 11.
2.0 is not good.
It’s called a borderline pass.
Got it?
Yeah.
But it’s okay.
Your mom has asked me to help you with this.
Even though you’re only going to be here for one semester,
I want you to adjust.
I understand that a sudden change can make you feel uncomfortable
but that’s how life is.
Unexpected changes can happen all the time.
This might be your first time so it’ll be a bit difficult.
When I had to move back from New York to teach in Thailand,
I had to adjust myself a lot too
because I was only familiar with the English language.
What’s See Luang in English?
Yellow.
Chopping knife in Thai? Ito.
Earthen stove in Thai? Anglo.
This is not the time to make jokes.
I’m sorry.
Let me tell you that all changes come with discomfort
but do you know how I got through those times?
I have no idea.
You have to find happiness in change.
That happiness will help you get through tough times.
Remember my words.
I will.
Thank you.
Anything else?
Director.
Hmm?
Can I borrow 200 baht?
Oh my god.
Hey.
You sell rice and curry here too?
You again?
Hi, Bad-Mouth-Kind-Heart Bro.
That’s not my name.
What’s your name then?
You haven’t told me.
Who’s even called Stir-Fried Clams?
Kang.
My name is Kang.
Let me officially introduce myself.
My name is Mok.
My nickname is Moo.
Nice to meet you, bro.
Mm.
You have to find happiness in change.
That happiness will help you get through tough times.
(I found my happiness.)
DIRECTED BY SAKON WONGSINWISES
Actually, being punished to live alone is not as hard as I thought.
Wait.
Do you know how to wash the dishes?
You live alone now.
You must learn to rely on yourself, you know?
I have you, Kang.
Let’s call it a day.
I’m tired.
Not yet.
My moves are still awkward.
My mom gave me an ultimatum to study hard and not get distracted.
I don’t want to hurt her feelings.
But we can work towards dreams and reality at the same time, right?
No one can stop your dream except yourself.
Things are not difficult
because you’re there for me.